# Ali Badawy

### Web Developer

Hi, I am Ali. A freelance Front End (Nearly Full Stack) self taught Developer based in Egypt. I specialize in creating Interactive experiences and functional interfaces using React, React Native, CSS and JS. Always had passion for Coding and mind for Business.



### **Work History**

#### Address

Bilgas, Dakahlea, 35631

#### Phone

01097114307

#### E-mail

ali.elbadawe@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/aliahmed-37973790



HTML	••••
	Very Good

CSS Excellent

JavaScript Very Good

Bootstrap v5 Very Good

Sass Excellent

Unit testing Very Good with Jest

React js Very Good React Native

Very Good

Git Very Good

Grunt 00000 Good 2020-01 -Freelance Web Developer Current

Freelancer, Mansoura, Dakahlea

- Coded websites using Vanilla HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with focus on language fundamentals.
- Created and deployed Mobile-First applications while learning new frameworks and skills.
- Designed and created useful API using JS and NodeJs focusing on user CRUD.

**Retail Store Owner** 2015-08 -

Current Jasmine Cosmetics, Mansoura, Egypt

**Accountant Intern** 2011-09 -

2014-01 Adwaa Al Moshtre, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

## **Education**

2006-09 -**Bachelor Of Commerce: Accounting** 2010-07

Faculty of Commerce - Mansoura University

Udacity Web Development Professional Track

### **Certifications**

2022-01

Udacity Web Development Challenger Track 2021-12

anguages

English Very Good

Arabic Excellent